{
    "took": 1,
    "timed_out": false,
    "_shards": {
        "total": 5,
        "successful": 5,
        "failed": 0
    },
    "hits": {
        "total": 23,
        "max_score": 1,
        "hits": [
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tb9YRyZp8EfrQ9_Ui",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "You will get the access after LAM request is “closed\"",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank You,Have a Nice Day.",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "Thank You,Have a Nice Day.",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Kindly get in touch with respective application owner .",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "Kindly coordinate with respective application support team. Or else kindly raise LAM unlock/Activate ID request for that application. Issue is not related to LAM. Does it resolve your issue?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_RequestForm.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to raise a LAM create id Request to that application or If you are getting “invalid id” error on LAM Page,unlock your NT ID\n\nDoes it resolve your issue?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Did you raise a LAM Request to take access of that application?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Sorry, this cannot be resolved at our end. <a class=\"btn-link\" onclick=\"openLink('Not able to login in Application');\">Kindly Raise a Service Request </a>",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Are you facing this issue for other than LAM Application?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Not able to login in Application",
                    "variation": [
                        "Not able to login in Application"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-kjQRDxL5ClbX1dMMu",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Please check if your PMS rater or Immediate reporting Authority is updated and also your reporting manager is visible in GAL.\nAsk your ER manager to update the correct Reporting Manager in HRMS.\nNote:Outsourced or Non-ICICI Bank employee need to update their Reporting Authority through NEES System. once all correct details are properly update in HRMS/GAL(only for out-source) it will take to reflect 24 hrs",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "The Authorizers are mapped by the respective LA Team (logical access team). Kindly check the Table C of the Access and Authorization Matrix and input/Provide the correct values accordingly in respective fields",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank You,Have a Nice Day.",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "answer": "\"Thanks for your feedback\nKindly Raise SR in IT APPLICATION CALLS_LOGICAL ACCESS MANAGEMENT SYSTEM_report an issue-LAMS\"",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Select any one approver and proceed to submit the LAM request. Does it resolve your issue?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Is the drop down blank after clicking  Select /View Approver(s)?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Is your role,location or Reporting authority has been changed?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Reporting authority not appearing in drop down before selecting Access Role",
                    "variation": [
                        "Reporting authority not appearing in drop down before selecting Access Role",
                        "Approving / Reporting Authority showing not visible or showing incorrect"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-kj3jGxL5ClbX1dMMw",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "You will get the access After LAM request is “closed\"",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank You,Have a Nice Day.",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "Thank You,Have a Nice Day.",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Kindly get in touch with respective application owner’s .",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "Kindly co.ordinate with respective application support team. Or else kindly raise LAM unlock/Activate ID request for that application. Issue is not related to LAM. Does it resolve your issue?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Raise a LAM create id Request to that application or If you are getting “invalid id” error on LAM Page,unlock your NT ID\nDoes it resolve your issue?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Have you Raise LAM Request to take access of that application?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Sorry. This cant be resolved at our end. Kindly raise the SR",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Are you facing this issue for other than LAM Application?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Not able to login in Application",
                    "variation": [
                        "Not able to login in Application"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-51JRfxL5ClbX1dMW0",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "question": "Application has certain Queststion pertaining to Whizible and Finacle details",
                    "answer": "OK we can test the same",
                    "variation": [
                        "Application has certain Queststion pertaining to Whizible and Finacle details"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-azwz9i0Pn1S39O-hT",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\n\nLAM application >Requests > Request Form > Yourself > Choose >Application name=I-SENSE > CREATE ID > Fill in the relevant details> Choose relevant 'Department Name'> Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nGo through the following Access And Authorization Matrix\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=12163&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\"",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-SENSE. Kindly raise a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-SENSE\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in ISENSE ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Getting error - \"Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense\"",
                    "variation": [
                        "Getting error - \"Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense\"",
                        "Branch is not enabled In I-sense",
                        "Unable to get data in iSense application",
                        "iSense  not working",
                        "Black Page after login into iView / iSense application",
                        "Your ID not found in I-SENSE",
                        "Account details are not fetching in iSense application",
                        "Unable to fetch complete details in ISENSE"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-ay3Gqi0Pn1S39O-hS",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx \n\nLAM application →Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name=I-View → CREATE ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nClick on below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \nhttp://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-VIEW.\n\nKindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access. Do you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in IVIEW ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Login issue in iView and iSense getting error msg : User not mapped with the application",
                    "variation": [
                        "Login issue in iView and iSense getting error msg : User not mapped with the application",
                        ""
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-aZaPSyZp8EfrQ9-0a",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "question": "Unable to take printouts in iView / iSense",
                    "answer": "As per the Business requirements, Print option has been disabled in I-VIEW.\n\nIf you still want to take print then you can take print by pressing “ CTRL + P “ on the I-View internet explorer window & then fire print.",
                    "variation": [
                        "Unable to take printouts in iView / iSense",
                        "Unable to take printouts",
                        "Unable to take printouts in iView",
                        "Unable to take printouts in iSense",
                        "Not able to take prints from IVIEW",
                        "Not able to take prints from ISENSE"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_trCvtyZp8EfrQ9_U1",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details → Choose relevant 'Department Name' → Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, <a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a>\n to read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day!",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "You must have logged in post 11 PM and the ID may have locked again. Kindly raise a new LAM request for ID unlock.\n\nDo you want to see the process to raise LAM request?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details → Choose relevant 'Department Name' → Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, <a href=\" http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a>\n to read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day!",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Your ID maybe Locked or Deleted in I-VIEW. So kindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see the process to raise LAM request?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Did you raise a LAM request for ID creation for this issue?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "As a compliance requirement, there is a 60 days policy-lock feature in iView, where in users who have not logged into application since last 60 days or more, their IDs in IView application will be locked at databases level.\n\nUsers can unlock the IDs by raising an unlock id request in LAM for application \"I-VIEW\".\n\nOnce the LAM for ID unlock is Approved & Closed then you can try to login in the I-View application same day or Next day before 11:00 AM or else the ID will be again locked.\n\nDoes it resolve your issue?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Error: User locked due to 60 day's policy",
                    "variation": [
                        "Error: User locked due to 60 day's policy",
                        "Your ID is locked",
                        "User id locked due to 60 day's policy",
                        "Message prompt on IView login page will be: \"User locked due to 60 day's policy\"",
                        "Unable to login as ID is locked"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-abgRui0Pn1S39O-hC",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com </br>\nLAM application > Requests > Request Form > Yourself > Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW > MODIFY ID > Fill in the relevant details> Choose relevant 'Department Name'>\"\"iview_branch_new\"\" > additional access role \"\"NO\"\" > Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role </br> (Before Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix </br>\n\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved the issue. Thank You!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com </BR>\nLAM application > Requests > MY Request > Search for LAM raised for I-VIEW > Check the Status of the LAM request. It should be in Closed state.  Then Click on Select option. Then come at the bottom of the LAM & check the Access role you selected. \n</Br>Do you want to modify the access role?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com </br>\nLAM application > Requests > Request Form > Yourself > Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW > MODIFY ID > Fill in the relevant details> Choose relevant 'Department Name'>\"\"iview_branch_new\"\" > additional access role \"\"NO\"\" > Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role </br> (Before Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix </br>\n\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved the issue. Thank You!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Do you want to modify Access role?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "For Accessing all the details in IVIEW you need to select the correct access role while raising the LAM request.</br>\nDo you want to know your current access role for I-VIEW ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Unable to view details in IVIEW / ISENSE",
                    "variation": [
                        "Unable to view details in IVIEW / ISENSE",
                        "Unable to view details in IVIEW",
                        "Unable to view details in ISENSE",
                        "Unable to load complete details in IVIEW",
                        "Unable to load complete details in iSense"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-aiUCei0Pn1S39O-hJ",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "question": "Unable to take printouts in iView / iSense",
                    "answer": "As per the Business requirements Print option has been disabled in I-VIEW.\n</br>\nYou can still take the print by pressing “ CTRL + P “ on the I-View internet explorer window & then fire print.",
                    "variation": [
                        "Unable to take printouts in iView / iSense",
                        "Not able to take prints from IVIEW",
                        "Not able to take prints from ISENSE",
                        "Unable to take printouts in iView",
                        "Unable to take printouts in iSense"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tbYA5yZp8EfrQ9_Uh",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application →Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name=I-View → CREATE ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\n<a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click here</a> to Read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-VIEW.\n\nKindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access. Do you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in IVIEW ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Login issue in iView and iSense getting error msg : User not mapped with the application",
                    "variation": [
                        "Login issue in iView and iSense getting error msg : User not mapped with the application",
                        "User not mapped with the application"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tcgGOyZp8EfrQ9_Uj",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "question": "Unable to take printouts in iView / iSense",
                    "answer": "As per the Business requirements, Print option has been disabled in I-VIEW.\n\nIf you still want to take print then you can take print by pressing “ CTRL + P “ on the I-View internet explorer window & then fire print.",
                    "variation": [
                        "Unable to take printouts in iView / iSense",
                        "Unable to take printouts",
                        "Unable to take printouts in iView",
                        "Unable to take printouts in iSense",
                        "Not able to take prints from IVIEW",
                        "Not able to take prints from ISENSE"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tkW93yZp8EfrQ9_Uo",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application >Requests > Request Form > Yourself > Choose >Application name=I-SENSE > CREATE ID > Fill in the relevant details> Choose relevant 'Department Name'> Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\n<a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=12163&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click here</a> for Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-SENSE. Kindly raise a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-SENSE\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in ISENSE ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Getting error - \"Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense\"",
                    "variation": [
                        "Getting error - \"Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense\"",
                        "Branch is not enabled In I-sense",
                        "Unable to get data in iSense application",
                        "iSense not working",
                        "Black Page after login into iView / iSense application",
                        "Your ID not found in I-SENSE",
                        "Account details are not fetching in iSense application",
                        "Unable to fetch complete details in ISENSE"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tnbEgyZp8EfrQ9_Uw",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW → MODIFY ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→\"iview_branch_new\" → additional access role \"NO\" → Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role \"Branch All“ / “Branch CSO CSM” / “CSO CSM Liabilities\"",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your query. Thank you!",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Access to the Insta Banking option in I-View is available only for the below user access roles: \n\nBranch All“ / “Branch CSO CSM” / “CSO CSM Liabilities”\n\nDo you want to see process for raising LAM request to access Insta Banking?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Facing issues with Insta Banking",
                    "variation": [
                        "Facing issues with Insta Banking",
                        "Insta banking page not displayed",
                        "Unable to opening insta banking in I-View",
                        "Unable to view Insta banking transaction",
                        "Not able to view Insta banking in I-view",
                        "Not able to select insta banking login",
                        "Insta Banking is showing \"you are not authorized to access\" for the link",
                        "Insta Banking option is not working",
                        "Application Web Server Busy error is being shown while opening insta banking option"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tkzuiyZp8EfrQ9_Up",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW → MODIFY ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name' →\"iview_branch_new\" → additional access role \"NO\" → Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role,  <a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to Read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → MY Request → Search for LAM raised for I-VIEW → Check the Status of the LAM request – It should be closed state→ Then Click on Select option → Then come at the bottom of the LAM & check the Access role you selected. \n\nDo you want to modify the access role?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW → MODIFY ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→\"iview_branch_new\" → additional access role \"NO\" → Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role\n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, <a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to go through Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Do you want to modify the access role?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "For Accessing all the details in IVIEW you need to select the correct access role while Raising the LAM request.\nDo you want to know your current access role for I-VIEW ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Unable to view details in IVIEW / ISENSE",
                    "variation": [
                        "Unable to view details in IVIEW / ISENSE",
                        "Unable to load complete details in IVIEW",
                        "Unable to load complete details in ISENSE",
                        "Unable to view details in IVIEW",
                        "Unable to view details in ISENSE"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-aTVTOyZp8EfrQ9-0T",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW → MODIFY ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name' →\"iview_branch_new\" → additional access role \"NO\" → Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com\n\nLAM application → Requests → MY Request → Search for LAM raised for I-VIEW → Check the Status of the LAM request – It should be closed state→ Then Click on Select option → Then come at the bottom of the LAM & check the Access role you selected. \n\nDo you want to modify the access role?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com \n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW → MODIFY ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→\"iview_branch_new\" → additional access role \"NO\" → Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role </br→ (Before Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix:\n\nhttp://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Do you want to modify the access role?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "For Accessing all the details in IVIEW you need to select the correct access role while Raising the LAM request.\nDo you want to know your current access role for I-VIEW ?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Unable to view details in IVIEW / ISENSE",
                    "variation": [
                        "Unable to view details in IVIEW / ISENSE",
                        "Unable to load complete details in IVIEW",
                        "Unable to load complete details in ISENSE",
                        "Unable to view details in IVIEW",
                        "Unable to view details in ISENSE"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-aiqSdi0Pn1S39O-hK",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Risk profiling for wealth customer is not enabled in iSense, you may get in touch with Jyotiprakash Dash(250393) or Harish Ch(256883) for further clarifications",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "question": "Yes",
                                                            "answer": "Wherever customer has iMobile option, guide him/her to do profiling through iMobile. \n\nIf above process is not possible, dummy modification at account and cif_id level as per iCore team clarification. \n\nAfter 24 hours the details will be available in I-Sense.",
                                                            "variation": [
                                                                "Yes"
                                                            ]
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                            "question": "No",
                                                            "answer": "Sorry this can't be resolved at our end. Kindly raise an SR",
                                                            "variation": [
                                                                "No"
                                                            ]
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Check the Customer status code in both  iView & iSense. Is there any mismatch in the status code?",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Sorry this can't be resolved at our end. Kindly raise an SR",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Is the Account getting properly loaded in both iView & iSense?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Is it a Wealth customer account?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Risk Profiling issue in iSense",
                    "variation": [
                        "Risk Profiling issue in iSense",
                        "Unable to do customer profiling in iSense",
                        "Unable to do risk profiling",
                        "Customer status code mismatch",
                        "Unable to do Risk Profiling for Wealth customers",
                        ""
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-al-Q5i0Pn1S39O-hO",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name= I-VIEW → MODIFY ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→\"iview_branch_new\" → additional access role \"NO\" → Select the current Access  Role and new Access Role \"Branch All“ / “Branch CSO CSM” / “CSO CSM Liabilities\"",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your query. Thank you!",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Access to the Insta Banking option in I-View is available only for the below user access roles: \n\nBranch All“ / “Branch CSO CSM” / “CSO CSM Liabilities”\n\nDo you want to see process for raising LAM request to access Insta Banking?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Facing issues with Insta Banking",
                    "variation": [
                        "Facing issues with Insta Banking",
                        "Insta banking page not displayed",
                        "Unable to opening insta banking in I-View",
                        "Unable to view Insta banking transaction",
                        "Not able to view Insta banking in I-view",
                        "Not able to select insta banking login",
                        "Insta Banking is showing \"you are not authorized to access\" for the link",
                        "Insta Banking option is not working",
                        "Application Web Server Busy error is being shown while opening insta banking option"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-a1D2ki0Pn1S39O-hV",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx \n\nLAM application →Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name=I-View → CREATE ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nClick on below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \nhttp://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-VIEW.\n\nKindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access. Do you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in IVIEW ?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "User not mapped with the application",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "User not mapped with the application"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\n\nLAM application →Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose →Application name=I-SENSE → CREATE ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nGo through the following Access And Authorization Matrix\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=12163&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-SENSE. Kindly raise a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-SENSE\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in ISENSE ?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense.",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense."
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \nBefore Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \n\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved our issue. Thank you and have a nice day!",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "You must have logged in post 11 PM and the ID may have locked again. Kindly raise a new LAM request for ID unlock.\n\nDo you wish to see the steps to raise the LAM request?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \nBefore Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \n\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved our issue. Thank you and have a nice day!",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "Your ID maybe Locked or Deleted in I-VIEW. So kindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see the process to raise LAM request?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No",
                                                                        ""
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Did you raise a LAM request for ID creation for this issue?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "As a compliance requirement, there is a 60 days policy-lock feature in iView, where in users who have not logged into application since last 60 days or more, their IDs in IView application will be locked at databases level.\n\nUsers can unlock the IDs by raising an unlock id request in LAM for application \"I-VIEW\".\n\nOnce the LAM for ID unlock is Approved & Closed then you can try to login in the I-View application same day or Next day <bold> before 11:00 AM </bold>or else the ID will be again locked.\n\nDoes it resolve your issue?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "ID is locked: User locked due to 60 day's policy",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "ID is locked: User locked due to 60 day's policy"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Kindly select the error you are facing:"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Login issue",
                    "variation": [
                        "Login issue",
                        "Unable to login in iView / iSense application",
                        "Lam request closed succssfully by the LAM team but still not able to login",
                        "Request for isense closed / Approved however access not yet given",
                        "Lam Closed with Remarks User Already Exist",
                        "Unable to login in iSense application",
                        ""
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tnD9RyZp8EfrQ9_Uv",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Risk profiling for wealth customer is not enabled in iSense, you may get in touch with Jyotiprakash Dash(250393) or Harish Ch(256883) for further clarifications",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "question": "Yes",
                                                            "answer": "Wherever customer has iMobile option, guide him/her to do profiling through iMobile. \n\nIf above process is not possible, dummy modification at account and cif_id level as per iCore team clarification. \n\nAfter 24 hours the details will be available in I-Sense.",
                                                            "variation": [
                                                                "Yes"
                                                            ]
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                            "question": "No",
                                                            "answer": "Sorry this can't be resolved at our end. <a class=\"btn-link\" onclick=\"openLink('Risk Profiling issue in iSense');\">Kindly Raise a Service Request </a>",
                                                            "variation": [
                                                                "No"
                                                            ]
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Check the Customer status code in both  iView & iSense. Is there any mismatch in the status code?",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Sorry this can't be resolved at our end. <a class=\"btn-link\" onclick=\"openLink('Risk Profiling issue in iSense');\">Kindly Raise a Service Request </a>",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Is the Account getting properly loaded in both iView & iSense?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Is it a Wealth customer account?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Risk Profiling issue in iSense",
                    "variation": [
                        "Risk Profiling issue in iSense",
                        "Unable to do customer profiling in iSense",
                        "Unable to do risk profiling",
                        "Customer status code mismatch",
                        "Unable to do Risk Profiling for Wealth customers"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV_tpoG9yZp8EfrQ9_Uz",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application →Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose ' Application name=I-View → CREATE ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\n<a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to Read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-VIEW.\n\nKindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access. Do you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in IVIEW ?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "User not mapped with the application",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "User not mapped with the application"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application →Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose →Application name=I-SENSE → CREATE ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\n<a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to Read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Your ID is not present in I-SENSE. Kindly raise a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-SENSE\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see process for raising LAM request for ID creation in ISENSE ?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense.",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Your Branch is not Enabled in Isense."
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, <a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to go through Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved our issue. Thank you and have a nice day!",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "You must have logged in post 11 PM and the ID may have locked again. Kindly raise a new LAM request for ID unlock.\n\nDo you wish to see the steps to raise the LAM request?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "<a href=\"http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to open LAM\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details→ Choose relevant 'Department Name'→ Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, <a href=\"http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true\" target=\"_blank\">Click Here</a> to Read Access And Authorization Matrix",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Hope this resolved your issue. Thank you and have a nice day!",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "Your ID maybe Locked or Deleted in I-VIEW. So kindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see the process to raise LAM request?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Did you raise a LAM request for ID creation for this issue?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "As a compliance requirement, there is a 60 days policy-lock feature in iView, where in users who have not logged into application since last 60 days or more, their IDs in IView application will be locked at databases level.\n\nUsers can unlock the IDs by raising an unlock id request in LAM for application \"I-VIEW\".\n\nOnce the LAM for ID unlock is Approved & Closed then you can try to login in the I-View application same day or Next day before 11:00 AM or else the ID will be again locked.\n\nDoes it resolve your issue?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "ID is locked: User locked due to 60 day's policy",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "ID is locked: User locked due to 60 day's policy"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Kindly select the error you are facing:"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Login issue",
                    "variation": [
                        "Login issue",
                        "Unable to login in iView / iSense application",
                        "Lam request closed succssfully by the LAM team but still not able to login",
                        "Request for isense closed / Approved however access not yet given",
                        "Lam Closed with Remarks User Already Exist",
                        "Unable to login in iSense application",
                        ""
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-kitWlxL5ClbX1dMMt",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Kindly clear cookies and temp file and try with below url.\nhttp://lam.icicibankltd.com",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "answer": "Thank You. Have a Nice Day!",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "Kindly ask your local It helpdesk Team to check/ remove all existing host file entries related to Lam lamteam,lamuat,lamuat35,lamteamuat,lamteamuat35 from the hosts file of your system(C:\\Windows\\System32\\drivers\\etc).\nSR Category for Local IT Helpdesk: IT-Helpdesk Path::IT INFRASTUCTURE CALL-->PC OR LAPTOP RELATED PROBLEM -->OTHE RPROBLEM",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                                        {
                                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                                    "answer": "1) Please clear temp folder first. (go to run –type %temp% then enter it will open the temp file path of system)\n\n2) Go to internet explorer click on Tools --> Compatibility View Settings --> Mark all the Check Boxes and add website“icicibankltd.com” and then refresh the page.",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                                    "answer": "Raise a Service Request in IT APPLICATION CALLS_LOGICAL ACCESS MANAGEMENT SYSTEM_Application slow or down-LAMS",
                                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                                        "No"
                                                                                    ]
                                                                                }
                                                                            ],
                                                                            "answer": "Is LAM page is load but header’s/Menu Option is not visible?"
                                                                        }
                                                                    ],
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Recently any changes done on your system?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Kindly use correct URL and try again. Does it resolve your issue?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "Are you using correct URL? i.e. http://lam.icicibankltd.com"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "LAM is not working",
                    "variation": [
                        "LAM is not working",
                        "LAM Page getting error"
                    ]
                }
            },
            {
                "_index": "chatbot_finacle_rd1",
                "_type": "i-sense",
                "_id": "AV-avc3ji0Pn1S39O-hQ",
                "_score": 1,
                "_source": {
                    "conv_ans": [
                        {
                            "conv_ans": [
                                {
                                    "question": "Yes",
                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "Yes"
                                    ]
                                },
                                {
                                    "conv_ans": [
                                        {
                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details → Choose relevant 'Department Name' → Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \n\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day!",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "You must have logged in post 11 PM and the ID may have locked again. Kindly raise a new LAM request for ID unlock.\n\nDo you want to see the process to raise LAM request?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "Yes"
                                                    ]
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "conv_ans": [
                                                        {
                                                            "conv_ans": [
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "Yes",
                                                                    "answer": "Open LAM URL http://lam.icicibankltd.com/LA_Index.aspx\n\nLAM application → Requests → Request Form → Yourself → Choose 'Application name=I-VIEW → unlock / activate ID → Fill in the relevant details → Choose relevant 'Department Name' → Select the relevant 'Access Role'. \n\nBefore Selecting Access Role, go through Access And Authorization Matrix from below url to Read Access And Authorization Matrix \n\n http://10.24.187.239/reportserver/Pages/ReportViewer.aspx?%2fReport2&aim_id=13196&rc:Parameters=false&rs:Command=Render&rs:ClearSession=true",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "Yes"
                                                                    ]
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "No",
                                                                    "answer": "Thank you. Have a nice day!",
                                                                    "variation": [
                                                                        "No"
                                                                    ]
                                                                }
                                                            ],
                                                            "answer": "Your ID maybe Locked or Deleted in I-VIEW. So kindly put a LAM request for ID creation under Application Name \"I-View\" to get an access.\n\nDo you want to see the process to raise LAM request?"
                                                        }
                                                    ],
                                                    "question": "No",
                                                    "variation": [
                                                        "No"
                                                    ]
                                                }
                                            ],
                                            "answer": "Did you raise a LAM request for ID creation for this issue?"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "question": "No",
                                    "variation": [
                                        "No"
                                    ]
                                }
                            ],
                            "answer": "As a compliance requirement, there is a 60 days policy-lock feature in iView, where in users who have not logged into application since last 60 days or more, their IDs in IView application will be locked at databases level.\n\nUsers can unlock the IDs by raising an unlock id request in LAM for application \"I-VIEW\".\n\nOnce the LAM for ID unlock is Approved & Closed then you can try to login in the I-View application same day or Next day <bold> before 11:00 AM </bold>or else the ID will be again locked.\n\nDoes it resolve your issue?"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Error: User locked due to 60 day's policy",
                    "variation": [
                        "Error: User locked due to 60 day's policy",
                        "Your ID is locked",
                        "User id locked due to 60 day's policy",
                        "Message prompt on IView login page will be: \"User locked due to 60 day's policy\"",
                        "Unable to login as ID is locked"
                    ]
                }
            }
        ]
    }
}
